welcome back my name is delen Grant and
this is now my sixth presentation on man
life
insurance and my insur just a brief
again review my life insurance is um
represent represent bability the
employees for bability for short-term
disability but the representation is
biased maybe it is good for some but for
me it has been biased okay um man life
insurance is located all over
but um although my uh place of work was
in
Ontario um my life insurance that dealt
with us the B the employees at B
Mobility was located in Montreal Quebec
Canada okay please feel free to pause
and read as I go along going to try to
go as fast as possible okay thank
you damages criminal acts yes their man
life has been deceitful in a lot of ways
and and uh and including murder attent
because of what they did yes it it
extended past 2018 to cover for their
deception yeah so they are also liable
all right
2018 um at part three of three
okay money life insurance company this
misc conscrew CBI report on the
corporate customer service job duties
for report on the CB bi Health Group
remember they're saying we have 51% of
idle time now I'm here to set that
record straight attempt number two to
sway the blame from B Mobility to say
our job was not that demanding
okay deception of the corporate customer
service department Frontline work duties
physical demands profile analyst report
on our duties were um was biased
highlights but ility deliberately waited
until the month of December 2017 you see
IB was asking for the report and they
deliberately from February I was denied
from February 2017 denied by
wsib and B Mobility waited until
December 2017 to do the report the
analysis report the analysis report was
completed in the month of December and
offseason month the month of December is
not included in our year end performance
reports as you have noticed I've been
through other presentation that clearly
stated that is not included okay man
life insurance F stated in their letter
that the analysis report was completed
on January 26 2018 mhm January to
November are very demanding months for
our job there are others who are injured
on a job not just just not just me
however my injury was worse report
stated that our department had 51% of
idle time that we had time to relax to
do stretches Etc this information and
and those below are fals the job tax are
deemed low risk for attendant of the
risk Etc that's what they're saying
right the job tasks are deemed low risk
right and then they're saying this idle
time include task where the mouse and
keyboard are not required
h
okay deception man life insurance
reported that the physical demands
profile analy report was performed on
January 26 2018 can you see it here I
have extracted it's on February 2nd 2018
right man life insurance report to B
Mobility okay
stated where to report to me and to B
Mobility because B Mobility would have
gotten that report right anyway let me
enlarge this for you okay it says
physical demands profile analysis of
your role customer corporate customer
service performed by Danielle Johnson R
Kim on January 26
2018 okay and I can remember this date
and I can and I can prove it prove it
wrong that this is wrong this is the
information that I have extracted okay
and then it says you can read here if
you wish but I'm some Rising as I go
along
okay 51% of idle time at our desk okay
here it is 50
51% at idle time okay feel feel free to
pause and read thank
you it was AR Rose one of the injured
employees at Bell in my from my
department rose was the one who
submitted that report to me on the 6th
of sep
setember yeah 6 of September 2018 and
she said I got the report from CBI that
that they used to the climb hour this
hour wsib claim so she got denied by
wsib to because of the
report okay and then she said I'll be
meeting the fir I'll be meeting the
first lawyer I contacted next hi Delan I
just came from a lawyer's appointment I
have some questions and all that and
then here she said good morning cuz
after all this right right I said on
18th of October see the time went I said
good morning Rose how are you I hope
that all is well I haven't heard from
her in a while and and then she said I
got letter from man life that they're
suspending my benefits as of O um
October 8 I guess the 8th of October
2018 okay I don't know what to do so we
are basically like in the same boat you
know
okay so interestingly here is a CVI
report let me read the top section
before I enlarge it for you a few of the
many deceptions physical um analysis CBI
the the CBI report right 1st of
December here and I'll bring it to your
attent I will I will enlarge I just want
to read right it says here um first of
December 19 this is it December 19 2017
that's what it when it was done and I
commented this is a low season month too
they said that we we get calls like 20
to 30 incoming calls per day notice per
day 20 to 30 incoming calls per day and
my response to that should be 33
incoming calls within 3
hours 33 incoming calls with within 3
hours not for the day within 3 hours
okay three they said combination of
calls and emails are 6 and 1/2 hours my
my response combination should be 7
hours with three and a half hours
basically
um with no sorry with
3.5 my bad 3.5 emails per hour within 4
hours let me read that again my response
to number three combination of calls and
emails are 6.5 hours that's what they
said right my response is combination
should be 7 hours with
3.5 emails per hour within 4 hours okay
so you see we got the seven hours here
okay
um 3 hours on
calls and 4
hours on emails so that's 7 hours okay
not 6.5 four they said idle time for the
day without any physical interaction
with the computers
51% so Logics now if we are online for 3
hours right with 33 incoming
calls and 4 hours offline to complete 3
and a half emails per
hour where was the idle time tell me
okay and I'll enlarge
this okay you may not be able to see it
properly but this is December 19 okay
where was ID of time when we have to
complete
3.5 emails some technical right per hour
for 4 hours some reps cheated H one
email sent several times to a client
counted as productivity and I did not
know that you see when you already know
know how to work the system I'm new so
afterwards I found out that they were
doing
that the the supervisor was aware and
tell them not to but they were still
doing it right while those like myself
who did not understood the system would
submit one email per client anyway I
would not followed them because that is
cheating okay sometimes have to wait
until break or lunch to make take a
washroom break yeah everyone knew that
the requirements were unattainable which
allowed many to cheat so Vis are warned
about cheating several times but it
still occurred okay so I
will enlarge this one and I have
extracted the information in green okay
and it says mousing accounts for 37% of
the work work day that's what they said
keyboard use use use accounts for 12% of
the day work day and an average of 51%
of idle time intermittent between task
this idle time includes CL where the
mouse and keyboard are not required
having 51% of the day um not requiring
the use of the keyboard and for Mouse in
it um provide substantial time for the
worker to take advantage of such periods
to relax stretch muscles typically used
all right so so when you add that up 37
plus the 12% plus 51% you get 100
huh
51% so we have more time to waste than
really working that's what the report is
saying they really think everyone is any
everyone is uh an idiot e cuz if anyone
could read this and accept this
something is wrong okay please feel free
to pause and read okay you will hear
noise in the background please um
uh um ignore thank you okay this is CVI
report and I comp I put this together
and luckily I had some I have some proof
to back what I put together okay all
right generated it's it shows here um
that Bell really were really
get really did US bad I tell you okay
discrepan is in the CVI group report
dated December 19 2017 and it says
Daniel and I said Daniel Johnson um
completed report on December 19
2017 right not January
okay the month of December will take
will will place the team if if they had
included as it says here the month of
December has never been included now a
yearly performance report since it is
considered the month with the least
activities least activities see least in
the month of December the month of
December would have placed the team at a
disadvantage of failing the year if
included in our performance all right
money life insurance stated that the
report has completed on January 26 2018
SE Falls report please feel to to um
pause and um review however this is
proof um 2015 it is showing that my my
year end report says below are delain
2015 year end results January to
November see right under line January to
November
okay and um these are my information
that I actually mine so it I'm entitled
to have it to present it okay and it
shows here um to back my to back what I
am saying okay
three this is
seconds okay would work out to be 5
minutes and 25 seconds supposed to have
of talk time ahd a average handling time
so this is a talk time per call each
call we are supposed to
handle we only have 5 minutes and 25
seconds if we go over the talk
time right if we go over um we are
penalized we fail okay and you have
productivity productivity emails
3.5 okay
okay
emails so we have the talk
time which we're online for 3 hours so
just just just think about it 5 minutes
and 25 seconds per call okay and then
you have productivity we have to do 3.5
emails per hour and we are on this for 4
hours okay and the same thing here I was
failing if you notice I'm a I'm above
3.5 and you know 3 315 I'm above but
anyway please feel free I and and review
okay July August all right and
here when I put it together this is 2016
this was the year that I was thrown
online and was not trained the
activities in 2016 were 315 seconds 5
minutes 25 seconds per talk time 3 hours
online okay and 4 hours for emails 3.5
emails per hour offline right reps were
expected to complete 11 calls every 5
minutes 25 seconds within the hour right
approximately 11 calls times 3 hours at
least
33 calls were expected for the 3 hours I
don't think anyone completed that but I
guess um whatever
I I I guess maybe I think they they have
you know why cuz there was one that I
told you about that I got I failed the
survey because they were bumping this
person no one wanted to deal because it
was too much so yes people were
attaining that measurement because
they're not they were not do um working
uh uh they were cheating the system
they're not helping the client they will
be cutting off the client so as not to
go over the 5 minutes okay please feel
free to pause and read with the 350
emails for hours is like 14 emails per
day and that one also reps were doing
that you know why because they were
submitting they were doing things and
doubling up and when they double up
right as I said did not know the system
when they double up it increased the
email wow they know to work the system e
okay the corporate customer service
department we have special it our shifts
we can choose our shifts and these are
the VAR feel free to pause and read this
was my shift I was the one with the 8
and 1 half hours I had an hour lunch and
um 250 minutes break but we all had
seven it's a 7h hour workshift the the
the the person who um reported and the
CVI report stated that we have 6 and 1
half hours to work now any which way it
took it it was 7 and 1/2 hours each time
okay corporate customer service
department on front line um versus
Corporate contracts desk back office I
am always back office from ever since I
left school I've never placed on front
line I am back office so at my age I'm
not that young um I was
placed I should be relaxing I was placed
basically um to WS it it it was not a
great experience at all I was placed in
an environment that definitely did not
suit me at all however I'm willing to
work but it was really demanding okay
the mobility inform form wsib that both
jobs were the same compare right they
said front office Front Line and back
office are the same okay that's that's
what the mobility reported so please
look and in the report it says the
employer has confirmed that the speed of
work was increased can you you see that
it was increased the speed of the work
was increased two the employeed indicate
that the job was larg the same okay here
you
go here you go it says the employer has
confirmed that the speed of the work has
increased Bingo however the employer has
indicated that job was larger the same
was not the same there night and day
okay and then here now Dr Erin's report
man life insurance specialist she did
say that I suffered from De of intens
sinovitis right that and that could
possibly be associated with the change
in position and change in our
workstation that's a fact one expect two
one expect this to be temporary and to
resolve after approximately 6 weeks
three she could be capable returning to
her previous position so if you look we
already went through this it's all there
and I've highlighted it in green and all
that okay pleas feel free to pause and
read thank you
here it shows this is back office all
along back office it was 3.5 Z emails
per
day per day 3.5 but it um increased the
lot part of um the mid mid 2015 it
increased to 5.5 emails per day and we
were doing it we were okay in 2015
productivity measurement at the
beginning of the year was 3.5 right uh
it was changed
5.5 um per day in July um contracts Des
emails were total for the month then
divided by the total hours worked for
the month um my result for February 2016
was 6.5 per day okay I was above Target
of 50 you know point I was 65 above
Target of 0.55 and as you can see
it
okay productivity the target was 0.55
and I was about above 0.65 and it was
per day now for customer service here
said that it is the same no it's not the
same we're doing 3.5 emails right 3.5 it
it thank God it didn't go to 5.5 that
would have been a killer but 3.5 emails
but it was per hour it was per hour for
4 hours can you imagine H five
measurements productivity see there were
five measurement with contract's desk
only three measurements one two 3 three
measurements 1 two three with um
customer service front line it was five
measurements 1 2 3 four five see them
see there 1 2 3 4 five and and as I said
this was productivity 3.5 and it was not
per day it was per hour okay please ref
free to pause and read thank you we are
not the same contract this productivity
productivity carries the most weight see
the
details okay it said here um
35% although this is 35% they said uh
productivity carry the most weight okay
and um it shows here that it was at 1.
3.5 okay Cas is per day then it moved to
5.5 cases per day and then guess what
happened since 2015 we were on the phone
for the entire day we used to be on the
phone like say 2 hours for per day 2
hours but then in 2015 we went to oh I
did make mention it prior two hours per
day um unlimited talk time
received sometimes zero calls or two
calls for the two hours calls received
not included as measurement it's not
included talk time is unlimited um calls
may we may receive calls for the day
maybe one call zero calls one call six
calls throughout the day you understand
from dealers and corporate CL cor and
the same
Frontline um work um workers we would
the front line customer service um we
would get calls a corporate contract T
would get calls so we weren't speaking
with outside clients you know we were
solving problems behind the scene
okay here now for the corporate um
customer service front line talk time
calls and productivity emails are two
heavy weights but all measurements are
important see details below okay and I'm
just telling you please feel free to
pause and read productivity email 3.5
emails per hour and um I will go
through it was it honestly you have the
fcr I I told you about it already at I
told you about the email um if you send
too many EMA it's only one email and if
you send through too many emails your
you failed but guess what happened the
Reps rather to fail fcr than
productivity so what they were doing
they were sending through like even say
one email they would maybe send it out
to the client maybe three or four times
to increase their productivity can you
imagine fail fcr but the productivity
was showing that they're sending out
emails okay please ref to and read thank
you here
um this measurement is for CCC the the
Frontline
workers these measurements actually okay
the aht the the CHT many of us don't
even know what this is case handling
time um and fcr email should sent out
once so you can please feel feel free to
pause and read oh let me let me deal
with ahd ahd average handling time 5
minutes 25 seconds per call right we
speak with the client while while we're
speaking with the client we are opening
various applications based on the need
okay and then while we're speaking with
the client we're taking memo notes while
covering a conversing with the client
right um update system with clients
requests add and remove incompatible
features future date and incompatible
features and whatever um complete memo
note as call ends if calls go over the 5
minutes 25 seconds per 25 seconds reps
do do not meet the requirements if you
go over you fail right we contract test
didn't go through all that contract test
does not focus on on fcr and HT and and
service and all that
okay please be free to pause and read if
you like
and this one is interesting because back
office as I explained we rece we we us
receive calls um just internal internal
calls all right as I already explained
so this is back office unlimited talk
time we can talk it's not it was not
measured so you can see the highest call
that I receive on in the month of
October was 6 and then you have other
months you can see just one or two or
zero or whatever but this is the calls
receive remember B said the job was the
same this is back office job that I'm
used to right and working on my own
initiative this is front
line front line total of
341 calls in a
month right it should be more calls that
this is what I did for the month of
August with my injured hand just picture
it huh with my in soulen injured hand
August 29 2016 I was able to receive and
process a total of 28 calls within
2.82
hours still below Target expectation was
33 calls 11 calls per hour you see how I
I'm not making this up e talk time per
call should have been 5 minutes and 25
seconds seconds 315 seconds I failed so
look at this not making up stories okay
I'm sure you have yes the reasoning the
reasoning capacity here look at this all
right this is close to it August
29th
282 the calls 28 calls in 2 hours hours
worked
2.82 basically call say basically 3
hours e 28 calls and I went over I tried
my best I should have been at
315 315 so I went over so I failed I
failed everything here everything okay
see each call this is three it's
supposed to be 3 hours 3 hours and the
amount of calls we receive so what what
idle time do we have you tell me okay
please feel free to review this is the
front line that they placed me on in
2016 can you imagine that's why my I
injured my hand it was too much compared
to this highest number of call received
in one day over a 3 month period was six
talk time unlimited talk time capped you
understand and for customer service
please feel free to pause and read thank
you
okay this was application for contracts
desk we have up like 10 applications um
with uh customer service front line
there was uh up to 18 there about okay
please feel free to pause and read okay
18 and we're while we're talking on the
phone we have to be opening these these
and addressing helping clients it was
really it was really um demanding um if
you hear sound please ignore I hope you
can hear me thank
you please feel free to pause and
read thank
you and as you can see I actually failed
the year
2016 I believe I was showing it to you
on the other slide um other presentation
how they man manipulated my results so
that they could place me last so a
corporate contract test with three
measurements I ended the year
2015 above Target I was placed 11th of
31 agents you understand as you can see
okay however your in report for customer
service they placed me last okay working
position possession for position sorry
for 4 months and 6 days May 2016 to
September 6 2016 off work on September 7
2016 with work related entry and they
placed me last okay and I've already
showed you what the did to place me last
anyway just showing you that
this uh our job duties were
falsified to
cover the slavery that they have there
within V mobility and making it seem as
if we are 51% of idle time be feel free
um to join me over on my other
presentations okay thank you for your
time